Hashmatullah Afroz

UK, Hayward heath, The Priory

+447860194058 | zaherhashmatullah1@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE -

I am an experienced software developer. I bring more than **five** years experience writing PHP full-stack applications, javascript, Django and more than three years experience in the technology industry. Duo to my qualification, extensive background, training, I am interested to apply for the vacant position and join your respected team. That will be really kind of you if you do a closer look at the particulars of my education and skills which you find on my CV. I am very confident of Management, Supervision, Monitoring, evaluation, Coordinating, reporting, Analysing, interpreting, team work, have good speaking voice, neat and respectable appearance, Ability and willingness of working outside normal office hours

EXPERIENCE -

2018 - 2020

Customer care

AWCC

Greeting the customers offer them credit cards and also, I was selling the cards in one side

2016 - 2017

Invigilator

British Council

Control and organize candidates during exam day

2016 - 2016

Teacher

Azerakhsh Academic Centre

English literature, 10 month program for teaching English Language

2021 - 2022

Freelancer

Diamond Gvm

I developed a CMS for the gym, it was a localhost database and I was maintain the database for them

2022 - Upto Now

• Full stack Web Developer

AM&M (Accelerated Mail& Marketing)

lam a full stack web developer in the company i am developing website for the clients and making secure and updating the websites, lam administrating the databases and doing IT works like upgrading windows, configuration of new PC with the network Iam also working with active directories **creating** users and managing them.

EDUCATION -

2018-2022

Bakhtar Unversity

Computer Science, Software Engineering

2017

· Habibya High School

89.89%

2015 - 2016

· Azerakhsh Academic Centre

English literature

2019

Udemy site

Web Programming Language

SKILLS -

- Basics of C/C++ programming language
- C# Programming language game development (Unity)
- Basics of Java Programming Language
- JavaScript (Full-Stack Developer)
- Basics of Python Programming Language
- FRONT-END Web development HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, JQuery, React.JS
- BACK-END(Server) Development: Laravel(PHP), PHP PDO, Magento (PHP), Express.JS (Node.js), MVC pattern, Basics of Django (python) MVT pattern
- DATABASE Development : MySQL(RDBMS), MangoDB(non-relational), SQLlite3(RDBMS)
- Mobile Development : React-Native(JavaScript) IOS and Android
- Networking and reconnaissance (PT) Familiar with Linux OS

PROJECTS

• Gym Management

Manipulating data, creating reports, Authorization, authentication and much more

Restaurant

Creating reports, Analysing Data, manipulating data and so on • My portfolio

You can check my portfolio here.

https://hashmatullahafroz.github.io/Hashmatullah-Afroz-portfolio

https://github.com/HashmatullahAfroz • **My LinkedIn**

You can check my skills in my LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/hashmatullah-afroz-0a53a0249

LANGUAGES

- Dari
- Pashto
- English
- Urdu
- Arabic

REFERENCE -

• Bezhan Rasuly - AWCC

Team Leader

+93700801773